クロンダイク殿より授かった
この力があれば　大門カイトごとき…。
With this power given to me by Lord Klondike,
I could easily deal with Daimon Kaito's kind.
（ノックの音）
（ホイスト）ヘルベルト様。
Sir Herbert!
ん？…　入れ。
Come in!
失礼いたします。
たった今　情報が入りまして→
Pardon my intrusion.
I have just received some news.
大門カイト様が　ご友人たちと共に
この城に向かっていると。
Daimon Kaito and his friends are coming to this fort.
何！？　なぜだ？　なぜ　この場所が。
一体　何をたくらんでいる…。
What?! Why?
How do they know about this place?
What are they planning?
いかがいたしましょう。
What should we do?
ん？　まあ　いい。
Well, whatever.
わざわざ　向こうから
来てくれたのならば→
Since they're going through the trouble of paying us a visit,
丁重にお迎えせねばなるまい。
よろしいんですか？
I think we owe them a proper welcome.
Are you sure?
よろしいに決まっている。　これは
私が名誉を挽回するために→
Of course I am.
This opportunity to restore my honor must be a gift from the gods.
神が与えたチャンスなのだからな。
大門カイト…。
Daimon Kaito...
lost te saguri de sagashiteta
Lost, trying to find it blindly with my hands.
tozasareta mirai no kotae nante doko ni mo nai
But the key to the locked future is nowhere to be found.
hashiru shoudou ima kaidoku funou
Undecipherable urges surging.
found kudaketa hazu no unmei wo
I found the fate I believed broken.
mijukuna yume no naka de kikoetekitan da
I heard it in my immature dream.
saigo made I'll be there for you
I'll be there for you till the very end.
tachitomaranai kono hari dake wa
I can't stop. I hear nothing else.
boku no asu wo kizamu oto tsukisasu
How this needle carves my future.
shinjitsu kara nigetara ima
I'm running away from the truth now.
genjitsu ni mo maketara ima
I'm losing to reality now.
nani ga nokoru no (nokoru no)
What will be left?
kazoekirenai kono kizu dake ga
The countless scars on my body
boku no kinou wo zanzou toshite kataru
are the only thing telling the story of my past.
unmei ga hodokete mo ima
Even if fate falls apart now,
sonzai wo kowashite mo ima
even if existence shatters now,
boku no michi wo yuku yo
I'm walking down my own path.
It's now or never.
This is what they say: "Live your life today."
There will always be, there will always be a way.
The Man Called Herbert
（ノノハ）ねえ　やっぱり　やめようよ。
オルペウス・オーダーってのが→
Hey, let's not go after all.
We still don't know just how dangerous the Orpheus Order is!
どんな危険な組織なのかも
まだ分からないのに…。
（カイト）フリーセルに会うには　ピノクルが
言ってたアジトに行くしかねえ。
To meet Freecell, I have to go to that castle Pinochle told us about.
回想
（ピノクル）フリーセルも救ってほしい。
オルペウス・オーダーから　クロンダイクから…。
Please save Freecell...
From the Orpheus Order... From Klondike...
Klondike?
クロンダイク？
回想
I can't let Pinochle down...
俺は　ピノクルの思いに
応えてやんなきゃならねえ…。
いや　応えてやりてえんだ。
でも…。
No, I don't want to.
But...
心配いらねえよ。
カイト…。
Don't worry.
Kaito...
（ギャモン）一度　腹を決めたあいつは
テコでも動かねえ。　分かってんだろ。
No one can change his mind once he's made a decision.
You know that.
ただ　確かに
クロンダイクってやつのことが→
But... I'm worried that we don't know anything about this Klondike guy.
さっぱり分からねえのが
気になるがよ。
（キュービック）ここだね。
This is it.
（インターホン　ホイスト）
「ようこそお越しくださいました。
ヘルベルト様がお待ちです」。
Welcome, and thank you for coming.
Sir Herbert is waiting for you.
ヘルベルト？
待ってたって…。
Herbert?
He's been waiting?
（アナ）開いた！
「どうぞ　中へ　お入りください」。
It opened!
Please, come inside.
どっかで　俺たちを
見てるってわけか。
So they've been watching us...
へっ！　上等だ。
Perfect!
行くぜ！
（一同）うん！
Let's go!
（ダウト）遅い！
He's late!
我らを呼び出しておいて　一体
どういうつもりだ。　ヘルベルトのやつ！
Why did that son of a bitch Herbert call us here?!
His disrespect for the dead is intolerable!
大体　死者を愚弄する
あの態度も許せん。
（ミゼルカ）本当なのかしら…。
ん？
Is it true?
ピノクルが事故死なんて…。
（ダウト）なぜ　そう思う？
Did Pinochle really die in an accident?
Do you have doubts?
それは…。
（メランコリィ）どうでも　いいですわ。
Well...
It doesn't even matter.
あいつってば　口先ばかりで
全然　役に立たなかったし。
He was all bark and no bite.
お前まで　死者を愚弄する気か。
あっ　ブー。
Are you going to disrespect the dead too?!
What's going on? Why are they here?
どういうことだ？
なぜ　やつらが…。
（モニター音　ホイスト）「どうぞ　こちらへ。
私が　ご案内いたします。→
Please come in. I'll lead the way.
その前に皆様は
これをお着けください」。
But first, I ask that you wear these.
あぁ？　６個。　１個多いぞ。
Six? There's an extra.
（ホイスト）ヨシオ様も　お着け願います。
Please put one on Sir Yoshio as well.
カイト…。
Kaito...
（ギャモン）俺たちへの謝恩会？
（ホイスト）はい。
A thank-you party for us?
Yes. Sir Herbert wished for it.
ヘルベルト様より　そのように
伺っております。
思いっ切り　うさん臭…。
Do I need to say that sounds fishy?
こちらになります。
This way.
なんだ　こりゃ…。
What is this place?
（キュービック）
こんな空洞が　城の地下に…。
I never would have thought there was a cave under the castle.
（アナ）アナが思うに　謝恩会って
感じじゃないんだな…。
I think... this isn't exactly a thank-you party.
（ギャモン）まっ　こうなるわな。
（ホイスト）ごゆっくり。
No surprises here.
Take your time.
（ヘルベルト）ようこそ　諸君！　私の
出世街道に花を添えるために→
Welcome to the thank-you party!
I'm throwing it for you, who came here in hopes of putting some icing on your "success" cake.
ノコノコと　やってきてくれた
君たちへの謝恩会だ。
まずは　私を邪魔立てし続けてきた
実力は素直に評価しよう　大門カイト。
But before that, I have to say that I'm impressed
by how you've successfully gotten in my way, time and time again...
Daimon Kaito.
てめえが　ヘルベルトか！
フン。
So you're Herbert!
だが　その才能が
私を本気にさせてしまい→
However, your talent has forced me to take this a little more seriously.
そのせいで　自身の無能さに
気づかされることになるとは→
It's ironic that your own talent will make you realize how powerless you are.
皮肉なものだな…。
（一同）あっ。
オルペウス・リングが２個…。
Two Orpheus rings!
（ダウト）何！？
どういうこと？
What?!
What's going on?!
As for those watching on screen, this will be a chance to repent.
（ヘルベルト）「そして　モニターで見ている
君たちには反省の機会を与える」。
クロンダイク殿より　唯一　ダブルリングの
資格を与えられたこの私と→
You will see the gap of power between you and me,
己の力の差を　目の当たりにし→
the only one other than Lord Klondike to be allowed two rings.
You will painfully realize how impudent you have been.
いかに　身のほど知らずだったかを
骨の髄まで思い知るがいい。
何やってんだ　バカ！
リングは１つだけでも→
Are you out of your mind?!
Just one ring puts an insane amount of strain on the brain!
脳に　とんでもねえ負荷を
かけるってのに。
貴様には　これより　世に
特別な存在である私のパズルに→
I'm allowing you to challenge the puzzle made by me, the most special person in the world.
挑戦させてやる。　感謝するがいい。
You should be grateful.
この城の中には　至る所に
パズルが仕込まれていてね。
This castle is full of puzzles, you know.
今回　その１つを　私が　じきじきに
改造してやった。　君のためにね。
I went through the trouble of repairing one of them.
Just for you.
いいから早くリングを外せ。　多けりゃ
いいってもんじゃねえんだよ！
I don't give a damn, just take off the rings!
"The more the merrier." doesn't apply to those!
持たざる者の　やっかみかな？
それとも　おじけづいたか？
The envy of one who has none.
Or have you lost your nerve?
そんなんじゃねえ！
That's not it!
（ヘルベルト）ここから脱出するには
パズルを解くしかない。
You can only escape by solving the puzzle.
素直に挑戦したら　どうだ？
うっ…。
How about you just challenge it?
分かったよ。
ここから脱出すれば　いいんだな。
Fine! So we're just supposed to escape?
そのとおり。　ルールを説明しよう。
出口は　向こう岸。
Exactly. Let me explain the rules.
The exit is on the other side.
貴様らが使えるのは　１そうの箱舟。
ただし　２人乗りだ。
You will use that one boat. It only holds two people.
そして　これより　貴様らは
全員　絶対なる理によって→
You will also be ruled by ultimate logic from now on.
支配されることとなる。
（ヘルベルト）
キュービック・ガロア。　貴様は　神となれ。
Cubic Galois, you shall be God.
God? What?
はあ？　神って…。
（ヘルベルト）アナ・グラム　悪魔。
ほえ。
Ana Gram, a demon.
（ヘルベルト）井藤ノノハ　天使。
えっ！？
Itou Nonoha, an angel.
Sakanoue Gammon, an archdemon.
（ヘルベルト）逆之上ギャモン　大悪魔。
Daimon Kaito, you are an archangel.
（ヘルベルト）大門カイト　貴様は大天使。
待て　こら！　天使は　俺様だろが！
Wait the Hell up! I should be an angel!
なんで　バカイトなんだよ！
うるせえな！
Why is Freakaito an angel?
Shut up!
（ヘルベルト）そして　最も無垢で
無能な存在である人間として…。
And the purest, yet most talentless human...
（キュービック）ヨシオ君！
Yoshio!
Let me explain the logic that now rules this puzzle. Listen well.
これより　このパズルを支配している
摂理を教える。　よく聞くがいい。
大悪魔は　大天使が
そばに居なければ　天使を食らい→
The archdemon devours the angel unless the archangel is present,
大天使は　大悪魔が
そばに居ないと　悪魔を食らう。
and the archangel devours the demon unless the archdemon is present.
人間は　神のご加護が無ければ→
Without the protection of God, the human dies in the presence of all angels and demons.
全ての悪魔と天使に
食われてしまう。
論理パズルか。
大天使が居ないと
大悪魔が天使を…→
A logic puzzle, huh?
Without the archangel, the archdemon devours the angel.
大悪魔が居ないと
大天使が悪魔を…。
Without the archdemon, the archangel devours the demon.
…んで　神様が居ないと　悪魔も
天使も　全員で人間を食べる？
And without God, angels and demons both devour the human.
なんか　変な設定。
That setting is just weird.
The ship can only be controlled by God, the archangel and the archdemon.
そして箱舟の操縦は　神と大天使と
大悪魔のみができるように→
設定してある。
往復できるのは　８回まで。
You can only leave and return eight times.
ルールに違反すれば　その時点で
この地下空洞は崩壊し→
If you break the rules, this cave will collapse and kill all of you in the ruins.
貴様らを　１人残らず
飲み込むだろう。
That's fine. But I have one condition.
分かった。
だが　こっちにも条件がある。
パズルを解いたら　俺とフリーセル
２人だけで話をさせろ。
If we beat the puzzle, let me talk with Freecell alone!
Very well.
よかろう。　ついでに　オルペウス・オーダーの
秘密から何から→
I may tell you all the secrets of the Orpheus Order as well...
洗いざらい教えようではないか。
もし　生きて出られればな。
If you can get out alive, that is.
貴様に対する恨みの深さ
復讐の決意…。
Learn how much I hate you, how much I want revenge,
己の命と引き換えに　思い知れ
大門カイト！
and pay for that knowledge with your life, Daimon Kaito!
オッドアイ。　早く終わらせねえと
あいつ自身が危ねえな…。
The odd eye.
We should finish this quick or he'll be in danger.
そうだね。
ひとまず　パズル自体は　まともだな。
That's right.
This puzzle is pretty straightforward at least.
配役は　ともかくよ。
ね　ねえ…
順番に渡っちゃダメなの？
The roles sure are.
H-Hey, can't we just cross in order?
まず　ギャモン君がアナを連れていって
次に　カイトが　私を連れていって。
First, Gammon takes Ana, then Kaito takes me.
（ギャモン）
それじゃあ　向こう岸に着いたら→
If we did that, the archangel would devour the demon on the other side.
悪魔か　大天使に
食われちまうだろう。
Kaito would devour Ana?!
（２人）カイトが　アナを食べる！？
Is that really what you should be caring about?!
反応するとこ　ちげ～し！
いやん。
アナも　やめろっつうの。
I'm delicious!
Ana, you stop too!
If Kaito took Yoshio, then...
（キュービック）例えば　カイトが
ヨシオ君を連れていったら…。
（２人）カイトが　ヨシオ君を！
Kaito would devour Yoshio!
はっ！　ギャモン君が私を食べる…。
Gammon would devour me?
違う！　大悪魔が　天使を食べ…
食べるのであって→
Hell no!
Even if the archdemon d-devours the angel...
ノノハが俺をじゃない。　俺がノノハを…。
あっ　あ～！
Nonoha wouldn't devour me...
I mean, I wouldn't...
ギヴァーは　やつだ。　どんな卑怯な
まねをしてくるか　分からねえ。
He's the Giver. We can't know what cowardly tricks he's gonna pull this time.
油断は　できねえな。
パズルタイムの始まりだ！
We can't let our guard down.
It's puzzle time!
（ギャモン）
そんじゃ　まず大悪魔の俺が悪魔の
アナと一緒に　向こう岸に渡るぜ。
So first, I, the archdemon, will take Ana, the demon, to the other side.
いいな。
ああ。
Sound good?
Yeah.
お～！　動いた～！
Whoa, we're moving!
もっと　スピードを出せ～！
無理だって。
Faster, faster!
We can't.
よいしょ。　バイバイ　またね～。
おう。
Bye-bye! See you later!
Yup.
ノノハを食べるな～！
（ギャモン）食べ…　食べたりしちゃ…。
Don't devour Nonoha!
I— No— What—
なるほど。　今のとこ
誰も食べられないね。
I see. This way no one gets devoured.
あっ！　ねえ　もしかしたら
次って　私とカイトなんじゃない？
Hey, is it me and Kaito next?
そうでしょう？　うんうん
だんだん分かってきたぞ！
It is, right?
I kinda get it! I'm not bad, am I?
私も　なかなか　やるじゃない。
あれ～？
Huh?
ここまでは　順調だ…　だが…。
It's going well for now, but...
フフフフッ…　それでいい。　そのまま
最後まで進めば　貴様の負けだ。
Very well.
Go on until the end, and you shall lose.
Sorry for the wait.
よっと　お待っとさん！
次　いくぞ。
Next.
あっ？　どうした？　カイト。
ん？　カイト？
What's up, Kaito?
Kaito?
何だ…　何かが引っかかる…。
Something... Something feels wrong.
（一同）ん！？
（ダウト）ホイスト　どういうことだ！？
Whist! What's the meaning of this?
なぜ　クロンダイク様は　やつに
もう一つのリングなど。
Why did Lord Klondike give him another ring?
クロンダイク様のお考えに疑問でも？
うっ…　いや。
I hope you aren't doubting Lord Klondike's intentions.
No...
なら　１つだけ教えて。
彼も　私たちと同じリングを？
Then tell us:
does he have the same ring as us?
いいえ。
No.
So you've given him a replica?
（ダウト）つまり　ヘルベルトには
レプリカを渡したと？
（ホイスト）はい。
クロンダイク様は　何をお考えなのだ…。
Yes.
What is Lord Klondike planning?
パズル　うまくいってないの？
いや　順調だ。
The puzzle isn't going well?
No, it's going well.
じゃあ…。
順調すぎるんだ。
えっ！？
Then...
It's going too well.
確かに　このままじゃ
８往復もかからねえ。
Yeah, it won't even take eight passes this way.
何か　インチキが仕組んであんのか？
Is there a trick somewhere?
何をしている！　早く次の一手を！
What are they doing?! Hurry up with the next step!
≪（キュービック）カイト！
うっ。
Kaito!
こんな所に　変な穴があるんだ～！
There's a weird hole here!
こっちも～！
なに！？
Here too!
What?
くっ…。
（キュービック）今　画像　送るね！
I'll send you the picture!
[TEL]
来たか。
This?
何　これ？
What's that?
心の声
こいつは　このパズルと
関係あるのか！？
Are they related to the puzzle?
心の声
あるとしたら　何のための穴だ！
If so, then what are those holes for?
あれは…　あの形は…。
心の声
Those forms... I see...
読めた。
えっ！？
Got it.
Huh?
Nonoha, has anything changed around here since we entered?
ノノハ　このエリアで　最初に来た時と
変わっているところは　ねえか？
変わってるところ？
Anything that changed?
そういえば　どこか…。
Now that you mention it...
あっ！　あそこにあるブロック！
That block! I think it wasn't there in the beginning!
最初　あれが　なかったと思う！
よし！
Okay!
こいつか。
うん。
This?
Yeah!
やっぱりな。
おう？　こりゃ　天使と悪魔か。
I thought so!
The angel and the demon?
そうだ。　たぶん　こいつが
出口の鍵だ。　運ぶぞ　ギャモン！
Yeah! These are probably the keys to the exit!
Pick it up, Gammon!
おっ　おう…。
（ヘルベルト）おめでとう。
うっ。
Congratulations!
（ヘルベルト）よくぞ　その鍵に
気づいた。　さすがは　大門カイト。
I applaud you for finding the keys. You live up to your name, Daimon Kaito.
いや！
こいつは　ただの鍵じゃねえ。
No, these aren't just keys.
なっ！？
見ろ！
（ギャモン・ノノハ）あっ！？
Look!
えっ！？　増えてる！
（ギャモン）天使と悪魔が一体ずつ…。
There's more!
An extra angel and demon!
That means the keys count as one person each as well!
つまり　この鍵にも　１人分の役割が
与えられてるんだ！
なっ！　って事は　こいつを抱えて
２人乗ったら　おだぶつって事か。
So if two of us take the boat with one of these, we'll be goners?
What?! That's cheating!
何　それ！　インチキじゃん！
ぐっ…　う～。
フッ　まあ　いい…
まだ終わらん…　まだな…。
Whatever. It's not over yet. Far from over.
So ugly.
不愉快だわ。
まったくだ。　ヘルベルトめ！
Herbert, I'm disappointed.
見てらんな～い！
I don't even wanna watch.
フリーセル様は　お残りに？
だって　まだカイトが戦ってる…。
Sir Freecell, are you staying?
Kaito is still fighting.
勝てば
僕に会いに来てくれるんだ…。
If he wins, he's gonna come meet me!
いらっしゃ～い！
Welcome!
相変わらず　ひどいパズルばっかり
作るのね　あいつ。
This puzzle is full of his usual cruelty.
いや　こいつは　これまでのような
ただのインチキじゃねえ。
No, this isn't his usual kind of cheating.
８往復も　かからねえことに
気づいて→
If you notice that it won't take eight turns,
駒が増えることを予想すれば
ちゃんと解けるように作ってある。
and predict that there'll be more pieces,
then it's made to be easily solved.
きっちり　８回でな。
はぁ…。
In exactly eight turns.
しかも　３往復目までに
気づけなかったら絶対に解けねえ。
And if you don't notice until the third turn, you can't solve it.
おもしれえパズルだぜ。
お疲れ！
This is a fun puzzle.
Thanks!
あとは　僕が　ヨシオ君を連れてくれば
終了だね。
Now I only need to get Yoshio, right?
Yeah.
（一同）あぁ。
（アナ）真っ暗け～！
It's pitch black!
（ヘルベルト）
このままでは　オルペウス・オーダーの
次期トップに昇りつめ→
At this rate, my dream to become the next leader of the Orpheus Order
いずれ　世界の頂点に立つという
私の大願が…。
and one day rule the world will be thwarted!
（ヘルベルト）大門カイトよ…　神さえも
ひれ伏す存在であるこの私を→
Daimon Kaito!
You tried to get in the way of me, someone who even God himself bows to!
邪魔立てする貴様に…
天罰を下す。
You will face divine punishment.
大門カイトに与えし大天使の位を
キュービック・ガロアに。
Daimon Kaito's archangel seal now belongs to Cubic Galois.
Cubic Galois's God seal will now change to Satan and belongs to Daimon Kaito.
キュービック・ガロアに与えし神の位を
邪神と変え　大門カイトに。
なに！？
ただし　邪神には
やがて再び　天罰が下り→
What?!
However, Satan must face divine punishment,
その姿は　醜いカエルになるだろう。
タイムリミットは３分！
and he shall change into an ugly frog.
The time limit is three minutes.
３分！？
Three minutes?!
That's crazy, Kaito!
無茶だよ　カイト！
ねえ　やめて！
Please stop!
（ギャモン）本気で行くのか！
ああ！　俺は負けねえ！
Are you seriously going?!
Yeah! I ain't gonna lose!
あの舟の速度じゃ
３分で往復するのは無理だ…。
Considering the boat's speed, he won't make it in three minutes.
どうするつもりなの…。
カイトを信じるしか…。
What is he thinking?
We can only believe in him.
絶対に解いてやる。
心の声
I'll solve this no matter what.
絶対に…　フリーセルを
心の声
オルペウス・オーダーの手から　助け出す！
Whatever it takes, I'll save Freecell from the Orpheus Order's hands!
貴様らの手には
すでに鍵がそろっている。
You've already got the keys in your hands.
If you abandon Daimon Kaito and escape, you will live.
大門カイトを見捨てて
脱出すれば　命は助かるぞ。
バカにしないで！
どんなインチキパズルだって→
Don't look down on us!
No matter how you cheat, Kaito will release the puzzle!
カイトが　きっと解放するんだから！
フッ…　インチキだと？
Cheat?
貴様ら　愚か者には
そう思えるかもしれんが→
You fools may think so,
今や　神をも　しのぐ力を得た
この私には解けるのだよ！
but I can solve it now that I have power that rivals God!
貴様ら全員　大門カイトと共に
あの世で解き方を考えるがいい。
You can all think of the solution together with Daimon Kaito in the afterlife!
哀れに嘆く　大門カイトの死にざまを
肥やしとして→
See how Daimon Kaito dies screaming pitifully
あまねく者の頂点に
私は君臨するのだ～！
and I rise to stand above all creatures of the world!
≪正解は　これか？
何！？
Is this the solution?
What?
ぐっ！　気づいただと？
He noticed?!
Let's do this, Yoshio!
頼むぜ　ヨシオ君！
行くぜ！
Go!
あ～！
お～！
ヨシオ君　行け！
Go, Yoshio!
やった！
よし　いける！
Yes!
I can do this.
くっ…　おのれ　大門カイト…。
Damn you, Daimon Kaito!
（キュービック　ギャモン）カイト！
Kaito!
カイト！
大丈夫？
Kaito...
Are you okay?
ああ　何とか
間に合ったみたいだな。
Yeah. Looks like I made it in time.
ああ…　よかった！
I'm so glad.
さすがは　ダブルリング。　かつてない
興味深いデータが採取できました。
Nothing less from double rings.
The data we've gathered is unlike anything I've seen before.
カイト…。
Kaito...
「こいつを鍵穴に入れんのか」。
「よし！　やってみよう！」。
Do we put these in the keyholes?
Let's try it!
ヘルベルト…　うっ。
Herbert...
（足音）
ん？…　カイト　何を？
Kaito, what are you doing?
ちょっとな
やり残したことがあるんだ。
I've got something left to do.
Go on ahead!
先　行っててくれ！
（ヘルベルト）まだだ。
まだ終わっていない。
Not yet... It's not over yet...
こうなったら　せめて大門カイトへの
恨みだけでも晴らして…　私も…。
Now... I should unleash my hatred for Daimon Kaito and have us die together...
あっ。
いいパズルだったよ。
It was a nice puzzle.
うっ　ふざけるな！
Don't screw with me!
確かに　俺は　ふざけたやつだ。
I'm really screwed up.
けど　パズルに関しては　ガチだ。
面白かったぜ　あんたのパズル。
But I know puzzles.
And your puzzle was really fun.
何だと…。
What?!
あんたの中には　まだまだ　すげえ
パズルが　いっぱい閉じ込められてる。
There are still many amazing puzzles locked inside you.
そいつらを解き放ってやれよ。
Let them all out.
これが　ファイ・ブレインに
最も近づいた男か…。
You... are the man closest to the Phi Brain?
全く…　かなわんな…。
I'm... no match.
もし　また会うことがあったら
次も戦ってくれるか？
If we meet again someday, will you fight me again?
当たりめえだ。
ならば　その時には　今度こそ→
Of course I will.
Then by that time, I'll have made a puzzle
貴様が　地団駄を踏んで　悔しがる
ようなパズルを作ってみせる。
that will surely have you stomping your feet in frustration.
正々堂々とな。
ああ。
Fair and square.
Yeah.
…とでも言うと思ったのか？
えっ！？
Or so you hoped, right?
貴様への恨み！
そうやすやすと　消えはしない！
My hatred for you won't go away that easily!
おい　待て！　何　勝手に
しゃべってるんだ　私は！？
Hey, wait! What am I saying?!
てめえ…。
何が　いいパズルだ！
What?!
A good puzzle, my ass!
私にとって　いいパズルとは　貴様を
地獄へ　たたき落とすパズルの事だ！
A good puzzle for me is one that throws you to the pits of Hell!
違う！　何が起こっているんだ！？
（一同）あっ！
No! What's going on?!
あの野郎！　やっぱり
だましてやがったのか！
That bastard!
He still had something up his sleeve?!
カイト！　逃げよう！
フハハハッ！　逃げられんぞ。
Kaito, run!
You can't run away! This cave will now collapse!
この地下空洞は　今から崩壊する！
何だと！？
やめろ！
What?!
Don't do it!
貴様を葬るためなら　この命
いくらでも　くれてやるわ！
If I can bury you for eternity, that's worth a dozen of my lives!
やめろ　やめるんだ　私！
Stop! Stop, me!
Kaito!
カイト！
やべえ　ひとまず逃げるぞ。
Crap, we've gotta get outta here!
カイト！　逃げて！
ハハハハハッ！　さらばだ　大門カイト！
Kaito! Run!
Farewell, Daimon Kaito!
（ヘルベルト）助けてくれ！
Help me!
これは…。
He...
あっ…　はっ…　カイト。
Kaito...
eiyuu kidori itsu datte shinjita muteki no kankaku
I think I'm a hero and believe that I'm invincible.
tatakatte iru no wa chikyuu no tame nanka janai
I'm not fighting for the world.
motto mai peesu de
It's for a more personal,
sou motto shoujikina negai no tame
a more honest wish.
nando to naku kizutsuite mo
No matter how many times I'm hurt